Polish Junior League of Connecticut Collection CPAA 88.11
Connecticut Polish American Archives
Polish Junior League of Connecticut Collection
1945-1988
CPAA 88.11
Connecticut Polish American Archives
8.5 Linear feet
The collection illustrates history of an immigrant organization for young women of Polish descent devoted to friendship, charitable work and scholarship. It cover years from 1926 until 1988. It contains correspondence, minutes and extensive collection of clippings and photographs.
Polish Junior League of Connecticut, Inc..
Biographical/Historical note
The Polish Junior League of Connecticut (PJL CT) was established in 1926 and incorporated in 1930. The organization's purpose was to unite "in fellowship the young Polish women of Connecticut, to combine their efforts so as to promote the welfare of this community, to all charitable work possible and make it of ever-increasing service to society." The PJL CT was a social service organization typical of many others, organizing a variety of events to raise funds for charitable and educational purposes. The types of events that it organized (most prominently the annual debutants ball: The Bal Menuet) were the same organized by other junior leagues. The distinctive feature of this group, which was a second-generation immigrant organization, was its combining of host society type functions with a clear ethnic identity. The Hartford New Britain Chapter dissolved in 1988.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
The papers were donated to the CPAAMC by Helen Gallant, a former PJL officer in 1988. Second donation of PJL papers was donated by Ms Helen Chaikowski of 975 Tolland Street, East Hartford 06108 and consists largely of PJL scrapbooks. Ms Chaikowski was responsible for publicity and was PJL historian. The donation was made in April, 1989.
Arrangement note
The original arrangement of the collection was kept. Folders were arranged chronologically.
Scope and Contents note
The collection consists of correspondence, minute of meetings, newsletters, financial information and extensive documentation of Bal Menuet. Rich collection of clippings and photographs add to a visual history of the organization.
Clippings.; Correspondence.; Minutes.; Pamphlets.; Photographs.; Polish Americans -- Connecticut; Polish Americans -- Connecticut -- Hartford -- History; Polish Americans -- Connecticut -- Societies, etc.; Polish Americans -- Correspondence; Polish people -- United States; Scrapbook
- President's Book
  - President's Book (1945-1950)- 1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - President's Book (1945-1950)- 1947 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - President's Book (1945-1950)- 1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - President's Book (1945-1950)- 1949 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - President's Book (1945-1950)-1950 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - President's Book (1953-1956)- By-laws changes, March 1935-October 1948., 1935-1948 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - President's Book (1953-1956)- 1953 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - President's Book (1953-1956)- 1954 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - President's Book (1953-1956)- 1955 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - President's Book (1953-1956)- 1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - President's Book (1957-1960)- 1957 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - President's Book (1957-1960)- 1958 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - President's Book (1957-1960)- 1959 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - President's Book (1957-1960)- 1960 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - President's Book (1957-1960)- Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - President's Book (1960-1964)- Meeting minutes, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - President's Book (1960-1964)- Various events, lists, finances, newsletters, meeting agendas, etc., June 1961-June 1962 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - President's Book (1960-1964)- Various events, lists, finances, newsletters, meeting agendas, etc.,June 1962-June 1963 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - President's Book (1960-1964)- Various events, lists, finances, newsletters, meeting agendas, etc.,June 1963-June 1964 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - President’s Book (1964-1965)- Various events, lists, finances, newsletters, meeting agendas, etc. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - President’s Book (1965-1966)- Monthly Meetings (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - President’s Book (1965 1966)- State Information (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - President’s Book (1965-1966)- Miscellaneous and Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - President’s Book (1965-1966)- Minutes of Rome Meeting (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - President’s Book (1966-1967)- Financial Statements (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - President’s Book (1966-1967)- Monthly Meetings (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - President’s Book (1966-1967)- State Information (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - President’s Book (1966-1967)- Miscellaneous and Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - President’s Book (1966-1967)- Minutes of Board Meeting (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - President’s Book (1967-1968)- Monthly Files (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - President’s Book (1967-1968)- State Information (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - President’s Book (1967-1968)- Membership correspondence and miscellaneous correspondence (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - President’s Book (1968-1969)- Monthly Information (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - President’s Book (1968-1969)- State Information, Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - President’s Book (1969-1970)- General Information (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - President’s Book (1969-1970)- Business Meetings (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - President’s Book (1969-1970)- Board Meetings (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - President’s Book (1969-1970)- Newsletter (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - President’s Book (1969-1970)- State Information (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - President’s Book (1970-1971)- Monthly Meetings (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - President’s Book (1970-1971)- Board Meetings (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - President’s Book (1970-1971)- Newsletter (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - President’s Book (1970-1971)- Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - President’s Book (1971-1972)- General Information (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - President’s Book (1971-1972)- Budget (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - President’s Book (1971-1972)- Business Meetings and Newsletters (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - President’s Book (1971-1972)- Board Meetings (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - President’s Book (1971-1972)- State Information (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - President’s Book (1972-1973)- Monthly Meetings (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - President’s Book (1972-1973)- Newsletters (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - President’s Book (1972-1973)- Budget (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - President’s Book (1972-1973)- Executive Board Meetings (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - President’s Book (1972-1973)- Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - President’s Book (1972-1973)- State Executive Board Meeting (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - President’s Book (1973-1974)- General Information (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - President’s Book (1973-1974)- Budget (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - President’s Book (1973-1974)- Monthly Meetings (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - President’s Book (1973-1974)- Newsletter (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - President’s Book (1973-1974)- Executive Board Meetings (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - President’s Book (1973-1974)- Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - President’s Book (1973-1974)- State Executive Board Meetings (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - President's Book (1974-1975)- General Information (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - President's Book (1974-1975)- Budget Report (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - President's Book (1974-1975)- Monthly Meetings (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - President's Book (1974-1975)- Newsletter (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - President's Book (1974-1975)- Executive Board Meeting (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - President's Book (1974-1975)- Misc. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - President's Book (1974-1975)- State Ex. Board Meetings (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - President’s Book (1975-1976)- General Information (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - President’s Book (1975-1976)- Budget (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - President’s Book (1975-1976)- Monthly Meetings (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - President’s Book (1975-1976)- Newsletter (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - President’s Book (1975-1976)- Executive Board Meetings (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - President’s Book (1975-1976)- Misc. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - President’s Book (1975-1976)- State Executive Board Meetings (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - President’s Book (1976-1977)- Membership and Attendance (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - President’s Book (1976-1977)- Budget (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - President’s Book (1976-1977)- Monthly Meetings (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - President’s Book (1976-1977)- Executive Board Meetings (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - President’s Book (1976-1977)- Newsletter (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - President’s Book (1976-1977)- Misc. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - President’s Book (1976-1977)- State Executive Board Meetings (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - President’s Book (1977-1978)- Officers (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - President’s Book (1977-1978)- Executive Board Meetings (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - President’s Book (1977-1978)- Business Meeting Minutes (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - President’s Book (1977-1978)- Newsletter (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - President’s Book (1977-1978)- Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - President’s Book (1977-1978)- Misc (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - President’s Book (1978-1979)- List of officers and chairpersons (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - President’s Book (1978-1979)- Newsletter (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - President’s Book (1978-1979)- Executive Board Meetings (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - President’s Book (1978-1979)- Monthly Meetings (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - President’s Book (1978-1979)- Misc. (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - President’s Book (1978-1979)- Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - President’s Book (1979-1980)- General Information (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - President’s Book (1979-1980)- Monthly Business Meetings (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - President’s Book (1979-1980)- Executive Board Meetings (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - President’s Book (1979-1980)- Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - President’s Book (1980-1981)- General Information (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - President’s Book (1980-1981)- Executive Board Meetings (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - President’s Book (1980-1981)- Newsletter (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - President’s Book (1980-1981)- Monthly Meetings (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - President’s Book (1980-1981)- Misc. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - President’s Book (1980-1981)- Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - President’s Book (1981-1982)- General Information (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - President’s Book (1981-1982)- Executive Board Meetings (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - President’s Book (1981-1982)- Newsletters (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - President’s Book (1981-1982)- Monthly Meetings (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - President’s Book (1981-1982)- Misc. (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - President’s Book (1981-1982)- Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - President’s Book (1981-1982)- State Information (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - President’s Book (1982-1983) (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - President’s Book (1983-1984)- Monthly Meetings (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - President’s Book (1984-1985)- Membership (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - President’s Book (1984-1985)- Minutes (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - President’s Book (1984-1985)- Board Meetings (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - President’s Book (1984-1985)- Newsletters (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - President’s Book (1984-1985)- Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - President’s Book (1984-1985)- Misc (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - President’s Book (1984-1985)- Committee Reports (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - President’s Book (1984-1985)- State Information (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - President’s Book (1984-1985)- Executive Board Minutes (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - President’s Book (1983-1984)- Newsletters (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - President’s Book (1983-1984)- Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - President’s Book (1983-1984)- Committee Reports (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - President’s Book (1983-1984)- Misc. (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - President’s Book (1983-1984)- State Information (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - President’s Book (1985-1986)- Monthly Minutes (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - President’s Book (1985-1986)- Board Minutes (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - President’s Book (1985-1986)- Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - President’s Book (1985-1986)- Newsletter (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - President’s Book (1985-1986)- Misc. (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - President’s Book (1985-1986)- 1985 Bal Menuet Committee (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - President’s Book (1986-1987)- General Information (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - President’s Book (1986-1987)- Minutes (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - President’s Book (1986-1987)- Board Minutes (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - President’s Book (1986-1987)- Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - President’s Book (1986-1987)- Newsletter (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - President’s Book (1986-1987)- Misc. (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Bal Menuet
  General note
  All Bal Menuet programs have been digitized and are available on the CCSU library web site under Digital Collections.
  - Bal Menuet Committee Meetings- 1954 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Bal Menuet Committee Meetings- 1955 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bal Menuet Committee Meetings- 1956 & 1957 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Bal Menuet Committee Meetings- 1958 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Bal Menuet Committee Meetings- 1959 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Bal Menuet Committee Meetings- 1960 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bal Menuet Committee Meetings- 1962 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Bal Menuet Committee Meetings- 1963 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Bal Menuet Committee Meetings- 1964 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Bal Menuet Committee Meetings- 1965 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Bal Menuet Committee Meetings- 1966 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Bal Menuet Committee Meetings- 1967 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Bal Menuet Committee Meetings- 1968 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Bal Menuet Committee Meetings- 1969 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Bal Menuet Committee Meetings- 1970 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Bal Menuet Committee Meetings- 1974 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Bal Menuet Committee Meetings- 1975 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Bal Menuet Committee Meetings- 1976 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Bal Menuet Committee Meetings- 1978 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Bal Menuet Committee Meetings- 1979 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Bal Menuet Committee Meetings- 1980 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Bal Menuet Committee Meetings- 1981 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Bal Menuet Committee Meetings- 1982 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Bal Menuet Committee Meetings- 1984 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Bal Menuet Committee Meetings- 1985 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Bal Menuet Committee Meetings- 1986 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Bal Menuet- Chairman's Book, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Bal Menuet- Chairman's Book, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Bal Menuet- Chairman's Book, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Bal Menuet- Chairman's Book, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Bal Menuet- Chairman's Book, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Bal Menuet- Chairman’s Book, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Bal Menuet- Chairman’s Book, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Bal Menuet- Chairman’s Book, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Bal Menuet- Chairman’s Book, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Bal Menuet- Chairman’s Book, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Bal Menuet- Chairman’s Book, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Bal Menuet- Chairman’s Book, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Bal Menuet- Chairman’s Book, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Bal Menuet- Chairman’s Book, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Bal Menuet- Chairman’s Book, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Bal Menuet- Chairman’s Book, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Bal Menuet- Chairman’s Book, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Bal Menuet- Chairman’s Book, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Bal Menuet- Chairman’s Book, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Bal Menuet- Chairman’s Book, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Bal Menuet- Chairman’s Book, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Bal Menuet- Chairman’s Book, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Bal Menuet- Chairman’s Book, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Bal Menuet- Chairman’s Book, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Bal Menuet- Chairman’s Book, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Bal Menuet- Chairman’s Book, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Bal Menuet- Presentation Committee, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Bal Menuet- Program, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Bal Menuet- Program, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Bal Menuet- Program, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Bal Menuet- Program, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Bal Menuet- Program, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Bal Menuet- Program, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Bal Menuet- Program, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Bal Menuet- Program, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Bal Menuet- Program, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Bal Menuet- Program, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Bal Menuet- Program, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Bal Menuet- Program, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Bal Menuet- Program, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Bal Menuet- Program, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Bal Menuet- Program, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Bal Menuet- Program, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Bal Menuet- Program, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Bal Menuet- Program, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Bal Menuet- Program, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Bal Menuet- Program, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Bal Menuet- Program, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Bal Menuet- Program, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Bal Menuet- Program, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Bal Menuet- Program, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Bal Menuet- Program, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Bal Menuet- Program, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- General Information
  - Polish Junior League Stationary (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - PJL CT- 50th Anniversary Program, 1926-1976 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - PJL CT- Challenge to use of term "Junior League", 1976 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - PJL CT- Articles of Association, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - PJL CT- Constitution and Motions to Amend (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - PJL CT- Motions Book- State Conventions, 1953-1985 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - PJL CT- Hartford-New Britain Chapter- By Laws (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - PJL CT- President's Book- By Law Changes (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - PJL CT- First Vice President's Book (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - PJL CT- Recording Secretary's Book- By Law Changes (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - PJL CT- Motions Book (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - PJL CT- By laws, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - PJL CT- By laws, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - PJL CT- Officer Lists (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - PJL CT- Hartford-New Britain Chapter, Minutes June 17, 1975- May 12, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - PJL CT- Ways and Means, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - PJL CT- Ways and Means, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - PJL CT- Ways and Means, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - PJL CT- Welfare Book, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - PJL CT- Welfare Book, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - PJL CT- Welfare Book, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - PJL CT- Welfare Book, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - PJL CT- Welfare Book, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - PJL CT- Welfare Book, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - PJL CT- Welfare Book, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - PJL CT- Welfare Book, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - PJL CT- Welfare Book, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - PJL CT- Welfare Book, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - PJL CT- Welfare Book, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - PJL CT- Chopin Centennial Program, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - PJL CT- 34th State Convention, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - PJL CT- 37th State Convention, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - PJL CT- 43rd State Convention, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - PJL CT- Art Show, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - PJL CT- Book Sale, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - PJL CT- June Dinners, 1982-1987 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - PJL CT- Loose Stationary (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - PJL CT- Ella Grasso Proclamation, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - PJL CT- Banner (43"x27"); Set of 9 wooden candlesticks with nine color candles used during oath taking by new committee chairwomen of a new PJL member (description of the ritual included); Gavel (Box 6)
  - PJL CT- Minutes, 1935-1949 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - PJL CT- Attendance list, 1932-1948 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - PJL CT- Constitution and by-laws: 1955, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - PJL CT- Hartford - New Britain Chapter - attendance list; 1967-1968, 1971-1988, 1967-1988 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - PJL CT- Membership letters and Information, 1931-1975 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - PJL CT- Membership letters and information, 1976-1988 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - PJL CT- Programs 1965-1975, program ideas, newsletter (1966-1973), 1965-1973 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - PJL CT- Program Chairwoman: comments and suggestions, 1973-1985 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - PJL CT- Bal, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - PJL CT- 50th Anniversary Brochure, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - PJL CT- Scholarship (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - PJL CT- Fashion Shows, 1980-1986 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - PJL CT- Bal questionnaire, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - PJL CT- Programs, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - PJL CT- Membership drive, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - PJL CT- 47th Annual State Convention, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - PJL CT- 48th Annual State Convention, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - PJL CT- Newsletter... vol.27, no.7- vol.28, no.6, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - PJL CT- Copies of standard letters (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - PJL CT- Stationery (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - PJL CT- Copies of new (1983) general info brochure (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - PJL CT- Copies of old general info brochure (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - PJL CT- Copies of new (1983) application forms (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - PJL CT- Copies of old application forms (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - PJL CT- Application for Membership, Sept. 7, 1929 - May 8, 1986, 1929-1986 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - PJL CT- May 20, 1962 Convention, Polish Junior League of Connecticut, Incorporated (program and miniature blank notebook) (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Polish Junior League of Connecticut Inc. - Articles of Association, 1930 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - PJL CT- Certificate of Adoption of Trade Name "Ball Menuet", 1954 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - PJL of Connecticut Inc. Hartford-New Britain Chapter By-Laws 3rd printing., 1976 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - PJL CT Hartford - New Britain chapter information brochure (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - PJL CT - Art show tickets, sales booklet, badges (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - PJL CT- Tax exemption application., 1984 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - PJL CT- Tax exemption application, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - PJL CT- Tax exemption application, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - PJL CT- receipts., 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - PJL CT- receipts., 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - PJL CT- receipts., 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - PJL CT- receipts., 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - PJL CT- receipts and disbursement, 1979-1984 (Box 8, Folder 13)